websitelooker.net 2017-03-09

# Privacy

**_WEBSITELOOKER.NET'S PRIVACY POLICY_**  
**Last update on September 18th 2015**

**TOPICS:**

  * Introduction and general terms
  * What types of information will websitelooker.net collect?
  * Does websitelooker.net collect personally identifiable information?
  * How websitelooker.net uses the information it collects?
  * Will websitelooker.net share the personal information with anyone else?
  * How is your information protected? 
  * Use of Feedback
  * We do not control Data Collection and Use Practices by Other Businesses
  * How to Change Your Information? 
  * Changes to websitelooker.net's privacy Policy
  * Contacting websitelooker.net about this Privacy Policy

**1.Introduction and general terms**

websitelooker.net is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy, which is a binding part of websitelooker.net's Terms of Use and End User License Agreement ("Agreement"), explains the type of information websitelooker.net collects through its website and the websitelooker.net.

websitelooker.net COLLECTS AND STORES INFORMATION ABOUT THE WEB PAGES YOU VIEW. ALTHOUGH websitelooker.net DOES NOT ATTEMPT TO ANALYZE WEB USAGE DATA TO DETERMINE THE IDENTITY OF ANY websitelooker.net USER, SOME INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THE websitelooker.net IS PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE. websitelooker.net AGGREGATES AND ANALYZES THE INFORMATION IT COLLECTS TO IMPROVE ITS SERVICE AND TO PREPARE REPORTS ABOUT AGGREGATE WEB USAGE.

Please read the following privacy policy carefully before downloading and using websitelooker.net or using the websitelooker.net website. If you use websitelooker.net you will be bound by the terms of the Agreement, including this Privacy Policy.

websitelooker.net provides you the information as to how much a website is worth. It does this by logging and analyzing the Web surfing patterns of websitelooker.net users, which we call usage paths.

websitelooker.net does not attempt to determine the identity of any websitelooker.net user by analyzing Web usage paths.

**2.What types of information will websitelooker.net collect?**

If you are visiting the websitelooker.net website (websitelooker.net), we collect the following information: the full Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") of the Web page from which you came to websitelooker.net; your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, which may include a domain name; the date and time for each page you view.

When you use the websitelooker.net, we collect information about the websites you visit, and the pages you view. This information allows us to provide you with information about the Web page you are viewing and to estimate as to how much a website is worth. The websitelooker.net transmits and stores the following information from your computer to websitelooker.net:

  * Your IP address, which may include a domain name.
  * The full URL of the Web page you are visiting.
  * The date and time the above information is logged.

All of the above information is logged together in a single data string for each Web page you visit. Each string is logged in our database in the chronological order received from our users.

**3.Does websitelooker.net collect personally identifiable information?**

Sometimes the URLs we collect through the websitelooker.net contains personal information about you. For example, when you enter information on a Web page (e.g., when you complete an online registration form or sign up for a contest), the operator of the website may insert that information into its URL for that or the next page. This information often appears after a question mark ("?") in the URL, although it can appear in other places. This means that your name, your address, your e-mail address, or similar information you might consider private or personally identifiable which you enter into a Web page sometimes becomes part of a URL that is then transmitted to websitelooker.net and automatically stored in websitelooker.net's databases. This can also occur with words, topics, products, or phrases you enter into search engines - whether those engines are provided by the websitelooker.net itself or found elsewhere on the Web - while using the websitelooker.net. websitelooker.net has no control over what information third party websites put into their URLs or where they put it, but any information in each URL is collected and stored by websitelooker.net.

websitelooker.net analyzes its logs of usage path, to determine Web usage of users in the aggregate.

If you e-mail websitelooker.net, we may store copies of such e-mail or similar communications between you and websitelooker.net. This can result in the collection of your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information you may have in your e-mail text, addresses, or other fields, as well as the collection of the your IP address, the Internet or other routing of your communication, and the date and time of your communication.

Although these information logs may contain personally identifiable information, websitelooker.net does not attempt to correlate usage paths or demographic information to your e-mail address and does not attempt to determine the identity of any websitelooker.net user by analyzing this information, except as required by subpoenas, court orders or legal requirements.

All transmissions between you and websitelooker.net, including e-mails, URLs, usage paths, and any personally identifiable information they might contain, pass through many third party machines, operating systems, programs, browsers, Web servers, networks, routers, Ethernet switches, ISPs, proxy servers, intranets, the public telephone systems, or other devices, any of which may create activity logs containing such transmissions.

**4.How websitelooker.net uses the information it collects?**

Your e-mail address is used to send you websitelooker.net newsletters, product updates, service-related information, and other offers and information from websitelooker.net or its business partners. websitelooker.net may contact you by e-mail to respond to reviews, ratings, and customer service inquiries you submit.

We do not disclose your e-mail address to business partners or to anyone other than employees and agents working for or on behalf of websitelooker.net, except as required by subpoenas, court orders, or legal requirements. We do not use your e-mail address to correlate your identity to your Web usage paths. If you have given us your e-mail address but wish to unsubscribe at any time, please see contact us for instructions on how to do so.

We use IP addresses to diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our website. Your IP address also is used by websitelooker.net to gather broad demographic information, such as your general geographic location and Internet Service Provider. IP addresses are further used to help determine the number of websitelooker.net users. This demographic information may also be used by websitelooker.net to analyze aggregate Web usage behavior.

We use Web usage paths to estimate website values.

**5.Will websitelooker.net share the personal information with anyone else?**

Your privacy is of core value to websitelooker.net. Except as described below, websitelooker.net does not intentionally disclose personally identifying information collected from any user to any third party without the user's consent.

We disclose any information we possess in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal requirements, and such information might be used by the receiving party to determine your identity, your Web usage and online shopping behavior, or other things about you. We generally do not inform users of such requests for information, although we might try to do so in some cases.

We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf, such as technical support services. To perform those functions, it may be necessary for them to obtain access to websitelooker.net's databases and servers, which may contain personally identifying information about users. They may not use such access or information for any purpose other than that for which they are retained.

In the event that websitelooker.net or substantially all of its assets are sold or acquired, all information collected by websitelooker.net would be transferred to the acquiring party. In any such transfer, however, such information would remain subject to any applicable terms and conditions, including the terms of this Privacy Policy and any amendment thereto.

**6.How is your information protected?**

websitelooker.net collects certain personally identifiable information provided by you. Your usage paths and other information provided by you can be accessed only by a limited number of websitelooker.net employees. websitelooker.net prohibits its employees from using any of this information to determine your identity.

**7.Use of Feedback**

All suggestions, comments, or other feedback concerning your experience with or use of the websitelooker.net that may be given to websitelooker.net ("Feedback") will be given voluntarily and without obligation or restriction of any kind. websitelooker.net will own all such Feedback and may use it for any purpose. Due to the nature of development work, websitelooker.net will not commit to correcting any reported errors or discrepancies. Feedback will not create any confidentiality obligation for websitelooker.net, even if designated as confidential by you. You will not give Feedback that is subject to license terms that seek to require any product, technology, or service that incorporates or is derived from Feedback, or any intellectual property, to be licensed to or otherwise shared with any third party.

**8.We do not control Data Collection and Use Practices by Other Businesses**

The websitelooker.net website provide links to various features, services, and Web pages provided solely by our business partners or other organizations. The links take you to pages provided solely by those entities, although sometimes the pages are co-branded with the websitelooker.net logo. You will be able to tell when another entity is involved with providing features, services, or Web pages, and any information about your interaction with those Web pages, including which pages and advertisements you view and any search terms or other information you enter, will be received by that other business.

When you click on links to other businesses, those businesses may attach a cookie to your hard drive and may collect information about you. websitelooker.net makes no claims or representations about what those businesses do or do not collect about you. Please review any terms of use and privacy policies of those other businesses to learn about their data collection and data use practices.

You acknowledge and agree that websitelooker.net is not responsible for any content, advertising, products, or other materials on the websites (whether co-branded with the websitelooker.net logo or not) of or available from other businesses that we do not control. You further acknowledge that websitelooker.net shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content, goods or services available on or through any such site or resource.

**9.How to Change Your Information?**

If you do not want to receive websitelooker.net newsletters, offers, and product and service information, simply contact us and be sure to include the e-mail address where such information is being sent, and state that you no longer want to receive websitelooker.net information and updates.

To submit requests to change or remove website owner contact information, please contact us. Please note that it can take up to 6 weeks for approved requests to be implemented in websitelooker.net.

**10.Changes to websitelooker.net's Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy may be updated from time to time so you agree to check it each time you submit personal information to any websitelooker.net's website. The date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page.

**11.Contacting websitelooker.net about this Privacy Policy**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy then please Contact us at:  
contact@websitelooker.net

**_Glossary of Terms_**

**Usage Paths**

A usage path is the trail of requests automatically transmitted to and logged by websitelooker.net as user surfs the Internet with the websitelooker.net Status Bar Addon enabled. Usage paths consist of the following data for each Web page visited by a websitelooker.net user: (a) the IP address assigned to the user; (b) the date and time the Web page is visited by the user; (c) the full URL that the site assigns to the Web page.

**Uniform Resource Locator**

A URL (or uniform resource locator) is the full Web address of a file or document you view when browsing the Internet. With most browsers, such as Microsoft Internet Explorer or Mozilla Firefox, the URL of every Web page that you view is displayed in a window near the top of the screen. Typically, a URL consists of four parts: protocol, server (or domain) where the file is located, path, and filename. However, some URLs have no path or filename. An example of a URL is:

http://www.websitelooker.net/company/index.html

http is the protocol  
www.websitelooker.net is the server  
company/ is the path  
index.html is the filename

**Internet Protocol Address**

An Internet Protocol ("IP") address is a set of numbers that is automatically assigned to your computer each time you connect to the Internet. When you use your Web browser to request a Web page from another computer on the Internet, your Web browser automatically gives that computer your IP address so that the data you request can be sent to your computer. For many users who access the Internet from a dial-up Internet service provider (ISP), the IP address will be different every time they log on ("dynamic" IP addresses); others may be assigned only one IP address that remains the same from session to session ("static" IP addresses) (more common with broadband ISPs).

**Domain Name**

A domain name identifies one or more IP addresses. Domain names are used in URLs to identify particular Web pages. For example, in the URL http://www.websitelooker.net/site/company, the domain name is websitelooker.net.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small data file consisting of numbers, letters, or other characters that a server sends to your browser and stores on your computer's hard drive. The cookie automatically identifies your computer, but not your identity.

You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.) However, if a browser is set to reject cookies, it may encounter functionality problems with the websitelooker.net .

**Browser**

A browser, short for Web browser, is a software application used to locate and display Web pages. Two popular browsers are Chrome and Mozilla Firefox.
